const rusPitanjaLvl3 = [
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "К О Р М А Ш А",
        correctAnswer: "ромашка",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "В А Н Д А Л А",
        correctAnswer: "лаванда",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Т Я М А",
        correctAnswer: "мята",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "М А Н И Л А",
        correctAnswer: "малина",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "З Е Б Е Р А",
        correctAnswer: "береза",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Б У Д",
        correctAnswer: "дуб",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "И Ц А К А Я",
        correctAnswer: "акация",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "К У Б",
        correctAnswer: "бук",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Г О Г И Н К",
        correctAnswer: "гинкго",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "П И В А К Р А",
        correctAnswer: "крапива",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Н А С О С",
        correctAnswer: "сосна",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Ж И Р И Н",
        correctAnswer: "инжир",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "П И Л А",
        correctAnswer: "липа",
    },
    {
        question: "Расположите буквы в правильном порядке, чтобы получить название растения:",
        letters: "Н И Л О М",
        correctAnswer: "лимон",
    }
];

export default rusPitanjaLvl3